BIOSECURITY AWARENESS
The threats we keep out
New Zealand's economy, environment and way of life depend on keeping harmful pests and diseases out.
INVERTEBRATE - Brown marmorated stink bug
INVERTEBRATE - Queensland fruit fly
INVERTEBRATE - Spotted lanternfly
INVERTEBRATE - Spongy moth
INVERTEBRATE - Red imported fire ant
INVERTEBRATE - Giant African snail
INVERTEBRATE - Citrus longhorn beetle
ANIMAL DISEASE - Foot and mouth disease
ANIMAL DISEASE - Lumpy skin disease
ANIMAL DISEASE - African swine fever
ANIMAL DISEASE - High pathogenicity avian influenza
PLANT DISEASE - Pine pitch canker
Anyone who moves goods, soil or equipment can be the first to spot one.
See something unusual? Don't touch it. Photograph it.
Call 0800 80 99 66
BIOSECURITYTRAINING.NZ